{
  "type": "quiz",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "&#19968;",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#20108;",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#19977;",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#22235;",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#20116;",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#20845;",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#19971;",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#20843;",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#20061;",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "&#21313;",
      "answer": "10"
    }
  ]
}
